Hello everyone. We often hear from
developers that building agents on the
cloud
>> [music]
>> today is fragmented.
Yeah, and if you ask your AI coding
assistant to help, it just gets stuck in
an endless loop hallucinating [music]
APIs. It can be pretty messy. So today,
we are super excited to announce Agency
CLI.
>> [music]
>> It's a single tool that makes building
and deploying ADK agents super simple.
Not just for you,
but also for your coding agent, too.
Like Gemini CLI, Antigravity, or any
other coding agent you already use.
That's right. Think of Agency CLI as a
bridge. It packages all the Google Cloud
tools you need into a simple command
line interface. But the best part, it
comes with a set of skills to guide the
coding agent throughout the process. And
that means your AI coding assistant,
like Gemini CLI, can actually use the
Agency CLI to build other agents for
you. Let's say I want our team to build
us an outage recovery bot.
Something that can automatically
investigate service interruptions. How
does this CLI actually speed up that
initialization process? Why is this
better than starting from scratch? It's
because I'm not writing any of the
boilerplate. I'm letting my AI agent do
it. I just tell Gemini CLI, I need to
build an outage recovery agent that can
parse server logs, classify incidents by
severity, and generate incident reports.
I also specify to use Google's Agent
Development Kit and deploy to Google
Cloud. First, Gemini CLI activates the
bundled scaffold skill to learn how to
create an ADK project. Then, it runs the
init command, which generates a standard
ADK folder structure. Next, it modifies
the boilerplate code to match our outage
recovery use case. Testing a few prompts
is fine for a quick check. But at an
enterprise level, how do we guarantee
quality? How do we definitely measure
that this bot won't hallucinate the root
cause of an outage? That's where we
bring in the evaluation harness. Before
deploying, I can ask the AI, "Run the
evaluations for the outage recovery
agent using the Agency CLI and show me
the results." You can see it adding
evaluation scenarios, which include
hypothetical user conversations,
expected tool calls, and judging
criteria for an LLM judge. The agent
then runs Agency CLI eval run. This
command tests our bot against the
scenarios that we just created. Oh, look
at that output. On our three test cases,
we have achieved a perfect score across
multiple criteria, including response
relevance, answer accuracy, and expected
actions. This definitely gives me more
confidence we can actually ship this.
All right, now we have a working
evaluated agent. But moving from a local
laptop to production usually involves
infrastructure headaches, like IAM roles
and secret management. How does this CLI
actually handle the deployment securely?
It can completely automate it. So, I'll
just tell Gemini CLI,
"Let's deploy this agent to Google
Cloud." The AI runs the deploy command
to push the agent to agent runtime.
Awesome. So, it's deployed.
But how does our actual team interact
with it? We don't want to build custom
front ends. We just want to interact
with this bot. We don't have to. We can
just register it directly to Gemini
Enterprise. I'll just tell my coding
agent, "Can you integrate this with
Gemini Enterprise?"
Now that it's registered, let's open the
Gemini Enterprise UI. Right here in the
interface, I can select our newly
deployed outage recovery agent. Let's
ask it, "Tell me about recent outages."
You can see that our agent is equipped
with the tools to securely access our
logs and help us debug the issue right
here in our everyday workspace. So,
that's the power of Agency CLI. We went
from an idea to a fully provisioned,
evaluated, deployed,
>> [music]
>> and published outage recovery agent,
with Gemini CLI doing all the heavy
lifting for us.
Yes, Agency CLI cuts down the busy work,
saves a lot of time and token cost, and
actually gets your agents to production.
Building enterprise-grade agents
shouldn't require navigating a maze of
cloud services. Install this CLI using
the link below and get your agents
closer to production today. Happy
building.